Inventory of the George Loft Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs, 1958-1979. (Box 11)
  - 35mm slides, taken by George Loft, 1958-1979 (Folder 11: 2)
    - Group G: First International Congress of Africanists, Accra, Ghana, December 1962
    - Group H: Dakar Colloquium on African Economic Development and Ways of Socialism, Dakar, Senegal, December 1962
    - Group I: Field trip for American Friends Service Committee to Dar-es-Salaam (Tanzania), Congo Republic, Nigeria, April-May 1961
    - Group J: Belgian Congo trips, Elizabethville (1957), Leopoldville (1958)
    - Group K: Mission to Mali, American Friends Service Committee resettlement scheme for Sahel nomads; women's work projects, March 1979
    - Group L: Lusaka, Zambia, October 1974 and October 1975, Self-help urban squatter upgrading scheme at John Howard Compound, led by American Friends Service Committee